Trust me, please.
Everything will be fine.
If you want me to stay,
I'm happy to stay.
Don't go anywhere.
Will you be my boyfriend?
I will, I will be your boyfriend.
I guess painless love does exist.
Tee, your phone.
Can you check who it is?
[Tee.]
[Where are you?]
[I really want to see you.]
[I can't take it anymore.]
[Can you come back to me?]
Fuse, I'm done taking shower.
Fuse.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
Baby.
Daddy is coming to you.
"I really want to see you."
"Can you come back to me?"
Ugh.
Tee, are you sneaking around with someone else?
Why do people keep going back to their ex?
You said you liked me, didn't you?
What's wrong, Fuse?
Did my brother do something to upset you?
Let me know.
I'll deal with him.
Where are you going next?
Going…
Where to?
Oh.
You came here this early.
Didn't you make a plan with him?
Ah.
Yes.
How have you been?
How is your class going?
Um.
Not bad.
Tee came to ask me for advice the other day.
He told me he failed one subject.
How could someone like him fail the exam?
He also told me…
it's the subject that he loves the most.
Seems like he misunderstood everything.
But I think…
he's trying to retake an exam.
Do you think Tee will pass the exam this time?
I think it depends on Tee.
Whether he genuinely wants to pass this exam…
or wants to take another exam instead.
When did you come down? You didn't tell me.
Thank you for the meal.
Tim.
What did you do to my person?
You shouldn't be asking me.
You should ask your own person.
Hey.
What are you waiting for?
Go make it up to him.
Otherwise, you'll fail the exam again.
No way.
I must get A+ this time.
Tee, you're pursuing me.
How could you manage to talk to your ex?
[Tee, where are you?]
[I really want to see you.]
[I can't take it anymore.]
[Can you come back to me?]
Jeez.
What are you guys doing?
I'm with my babe.
Let me hold it for you, babe. I gotta go.
Mo.
I'm pooping. Let me hang up first.
Frame.
We're here for the makeup exam.
The teacher just called us, we've to go.
Hey
Hey.
Ugh.
No one is free to call me.
What's wrong? Why did you eat so little today?
Oh.
Do you want something else to eat?
Like me?
Won't you play along?
Why did you call your friends earlier?
You don't want to be with me anymore?
I'm the one who should have said that.
What?
Have you replied her yet?
Reply to whom?
Or did you guys secretly
talk to each other without telling me?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Tee, look into my eyes.
They say liars avoid eye contact.
Who told you that?
Tee.
I won't avoid your gaze.
And I'll hold you in my arms as well.
Why are you sulking? Talk to me.
Your ex.
My ex?
Check your chat.
[If you don't reply, I'll call you.]
Hello?
Where are you? Can you come over here?
I want to see you.
I'm busy right now.
Even you don't care about me?
Why is the world so mean to me?
If you don't show up, I'll end my life.
(Fuse) End her life? (Tee) End her life?
Hurry up, I'm waiting at our usual place.
Why are you making that face?
I brought you along with me.
Are you still overthinking?
You still haven't told me…
who Baikhao is.
Baikhao is my ex.
Well, I'm off.
Hey.
We broke up a long time ago.
We're really just friends right now.
You sure?
Absolutely.
That's why I brought you along.
So you don't have to overthink it on your own.
And you'll know that…
You're the only one I love.
Fine, let's head over.
I wonder if she's okay by now.
Come on.
[Baikhao]
Tee.
I really miss you.
This one is good.
You should try some.
Hey.
This is Fuse.
My friend.
This is Baikhao.
Hi.
Is he your new friend?
I've never seen him before.
He seems a bit rude.
I normally see you hanging around with Champ and Copter.
I've been closest to him lately.
Oh, really?
How envious.
How are you doing?
About what you tell me.
About I'm going to end my life?
Huh.
I'm not going to die easily.
As long as she's still breathing,
I refuse to die.
Who are you talking about?
The person who Babe liked her post.
It's driving me crazy.
There are millions of profiles on IG,
And yet he chose to like her post.
I already told Babe that…
If this happens one more time,
we're done.
Mark my words.
I'm done for real this time.
Am I not good enough?
Why did he have to like her post?
Baikhao, chill out.
Have you talked to you boyfriend?
He might have misclicked.
No, I won't talk to him.
I already blocked him and I'll throw my phone away.
Wait, wait.
Chill out.
Take it easy.
Did someone say my name?
Babe.
I'm sorry.
You've got it wrong.
Hear me out, please.
Why didn't you tell me in the first place?
You blocked me.
Let's head back. I want to go home.
Okay.
What just happened?
Well, it's Baikhao and her boyfriend.
I already knew that.
Are you messing with me?
She is usually like this.
Always arguing with her boyfriend.
But they actually love each other.
She's fighting with her boyfriend,
and yet she calls you?
Why?
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm just asking.
So that means I can meet her again in the future?
Tee.
I'm kidding.
Baikhao and I are just friends.
Can you really be friends with an ex?
I can be friends with everyone…
except one person.
Who?
It's you.
Are you gonna cutting me off?
Are you stupid?
Huh?
What did you say?
Nothing.
If it bothers you, I can block her.
It's okay.
Tee, you don't have to.
She's your friend.
I'm also your friend.
It's not my place to to stop you.
You can.
Who am I to to stop you?
Hey, Fuse.
Let's go on a trip.
Wit's resort will cover everything.
Free food and accommodation.
Super chill.
Hey, it's not like that.
Cool, I'm in.
Great, see you at school tomorrow.
Whoa, let's go.
Tomorrow?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Leaving tomorrow?
Will you go on a trip with me?
Sure.
Um.
On this trip,
I think…
I'll ask Tee to be my boyfriend.
Go for it.
I'll help you.
Let's go.
Let's go on a trip.
Hey.
Hotties.
Yeah, fox-like top.
Hey.
Puupy boy.
Woof-woof.
Tanned country boy.
Thanks.
Ouch.
Nerd, come here.
Good things are meant to be shared,
but don't linger. The owner is jealous.
The owner is so scary.
Is that Tee, your crush?
Yep. He already look handsome in the uniform,…
but he look even more handsome in casual clothes.
I heard that he's single.
Go for him.
No way.
Hmm?
Do you like it when people stare at you?
Oh, no no no.
What's up, bro?
Yay, bro.
Wit's driver is here, let's go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Tee, you go ahead.
I need to pee.
Give me your bag. I'll carry it.
Thanks.
Hurry up.
Mo.
What?
Can I ask your advice on something?
Go ahead.
I've been thinking…
I think…
Hey.
By the time you say it,
I'll already be at Khao Yai.
Fine.
I'll talk.
On this trip,
I think…
I'lll ask Tee to be my boyfriend.
Go for it, I'll help you.
Really?
Yeah, trust me on this.
You sure?
Wanna go?
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
Can I really trust you?
I think it's better than the picture.
Seriously?
Yeah.
It's pretty.
Right, I feel like going in the water.
Who's coming with me?
Is there a place for swimming?
There is.
Hey, I think we should try it this afternoon.
You down?
I'm down.
Me too.
Right.
Fuse, do you think this place looks familiar?
We have been here before, right?
Um, I think you're right.
Shoot.
Wow, Wit.
Your resort is amazing.
Whoa.
Ouch.
Wit.
Whoa.
Alright.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Hurry up.
Fine.
Make it quick.
Who texted you?
My sibling.
Men or women?
Women.
She's my older sister.
Real older sister.
She looks like me in a wig.
You in a wig?
I want to see you in a wig.
Then pulling off the wig of the person next to you.
Hey.
Whoa, easy.
This is my real hair.
I'm joking.
I just think you're cute.
Hey, hey.
Look, do we look alike?
Are you still talking with those people?
Those people?
You told me you have a lot of options.
Nah.
I already have my boyfriend.
I've cut ties with all of them.
If you don't trust me,
you can check my phone.
I'll give you my password.
No.
I don't want to know your password at all.
I just want to trust you.
You can trust me.
Because…
I truly have only you.
My wife is the sexiest in the world.
Especially when…
When?
You don't have to know that.
How about you, Fuse?
Other couples is so in love,
leaving only you.
I'm also happy.
Happy? You sure?
Great. I'm leaving then.
Hey.
I thought you would help me.
Listen up, kid.
I guarantee you.
After this trip,
you'll have a boyfriend.
What will you do?
Just trust me.
Guys.
I'm back.
Wit.
How many rooms did you book?
Hey, I want a big one.
I want a bathtub.
I want a room with a mountain view.
I want a soundproof room.
Frame.
I just want to play some music.
Uh, guys…
I saw that you guys were coming.
So I told my dad…
I wanted to go camping.
Camping?
That's a huge pile of dog poop.
Hey, will you go camping with me?
Let's go.
Hold on, you have to crawl out quietly.
Why?
There is the enemy.
Yeah, they might take us down.
Wit.
Huh?
No AC?
You know what…
it will be really cold at night.
Wit.
What about the bathroom?
The bathroom?
It's right here.
What?
Hey, I'm kidding.
It's over there.
Ah.
Wait.
So we have to take a shower together then?
Yeah.
I thought I signed up for a boy scout camp.
Hey.
But I think it's great.
If we sleep in tents,
we can look at the stars together.
Sleeping in tents sounds nice though.
I like it.
I agree.
We'll put our things away first.
I can sleep here. It's perfect.
Really?
Um.
Let's go.
Book.
How about doing it in a new place?
Ugh.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
Wit.
I want to ride an ATV.
Okay, I'm in.
Let's go then.
Come on.
I was just thinking about riding an ATV.
Let's head over.
Tee.
Hmm?
Can you sleep in a tent?
Um… I can't.
Oh, what do we do?
I can't sleep,
unless you kiss me.
Tee.
Our friends might see us.
There is no one around here.
Give me a kiss.
Hurry up.
Only a cheek kiss.
Fuse, let's ride an ATV.
What are you doing?
Hey.
What's up, man?
Uh…
No… Nothing.
Hey.
Since we're already on a trip,
let's go wild and crazy.
Alright, I'm in.
Let's go.
Tee, are you tired?
Nope, I just want to take a break.
Aren't you cold?
Move closer.
Hurry up, or you might catch a cold.
Is this good?
It's good.
How about this?
So good.
I'm so happy.
For being here with you.
After we finishing our high school,
will we ever come back here again?
Sure.
What about when we're in college?
Can we come back here?
Of course.
What about when we're working? Will we come here?
We will. I always down to come here with you.
But not as a friend.
I want to go everywhere with you.
As a…
Hey, hey.
Hey.
There are literally so many of us here.
How can you two just be lovey-dovey by yourselves?
Get down here if you're man enough.
Yeah.
Get down here.
Come on.
Fine, you asked for it.
What's that over there?
Why is it so dark?
Over there?
A murder took place right there.
Oh!
What's that?
Ugh, I can't keep up with you guys.
You can have mine first.
It's okay.
Here, take mine.
Give that to me.
Hey.
Can I get a fan for my boyfriend?
He's sweating.
Frame.
What?
Can I borrow your fan?
My boyfriend is using it.
You should bring your own next time.
It's okay.
I can use this instead.
You sure?
Um, can't I?
Absolutely.
Get ready to catch.
Let me fan you.
Tee.
If you keep shooing away mosquitoes for me,
when are you going to eat?
Feed me then.
Hey, we're hanging out as a group,
not as couples like you guys.
Yeah, split up.
Why do you stick with your partner?
Separate. Split up.
I won't, I want to sit with my wife.
You can't.
Frame, you should sit somewhere else.
I want to sit with Yok.
Huh?
Over there.
What?
Come here.
Come on.
Let's have some pizza.
Let's eat.
Are gonna finish a whole pizza?
Hey.
Mo.
The day is almost over.
I still haven't asked him to be my boyfriend yet.
It's okay.
Trust me.
Leave it to me.
Wit.
Huh?
What's that over there?
Why is it so dark?
Over there?
A murder took place right there.
Gosh!
Are you scared?
I'm not.
Wit, tell us the story.
Fuse.
Alright.
I only know the rough details…
since it happened before I was born.
At that time, two guests came to stay.
A woman and a man.
But when checking out,
there were only a man checking out.
Until the housekeeper went in to clean,
she found…
nothing.
Ugh.
Wit.
Alright, I'll tell it right this time.
Listen carefully.
The housekeeper…
bent down to clean under the bench,
she saw…
a dust.
Gosh!
Ugh.
Wit.
Alright.
The body of that woman…
was drenched in blood.
Oh.
After that incident,
some guests who stayed here…
said that…
they heard a women laughing…
and crying.
But some of them…
saw the woman sitting on the bench.
My dad had to invite a monk for chanting,
but it didn't hep at all.
So he decided to leave that bench…
in a storage.
And nobody dared to touch it ever again.
That's the story.
Let's do a test.
A test?
A test of courage.
Whoever brave enough to take a selfie with the bench,
I'll carry your bag all day tomorrow.
Ugh.
Save it.
I can carry my wife's bag.
Frame.
I told you not to call me as a wife.
I'm out. It looks so dusty.
My skin will break out.
I'm out. It's nonsense.
I agree with you.
Or…
are you guys still scared of ghosts?
You're in the 11th grade now.
I'll do it.
Who are you going with?
With Tee, obviously.
Hey, Fuse.
Are you gonna let a 10th grade kid look down on us like this?
We need to prove to this kid…
that ghosts aren't exist.
Only taking a photo, right?
Let's go, Tee.
You got this.
Come on, you can do it.
Are you scared?
Shall we go back?
If you're scared, why did you come?
I won't go back.
Rodtang will laugh at us.
Are you scared?
I'm more scared of people.
What if there is a robber in here?
Give it to me.
Stand behind me then.
Hold on, I think just a front shot is enough.
No way, they're gonna think we're chickens.
Let's make it quick and head back.
Gosh!
Oh!
What's that?
What's going on?
What happened?
Tee, what's that?
A bowl.
It scared me.
Oh!
A Buddha statue. We apologize.
Tee.
Is this the bench?
The one that had a body under it?
Hey.
Don't say like that.
Alright, let's take a photo and head back.
Won't you check the photos?
No way, I'm afraid I will spot something else.
If you're this scared,
you don't have to do it in the first place.
Because I'll carry your bag anyway tomorrow.
Alright, let's head back.
You're not heading back?
I came here…
just because I wanted to be with you alone.
Do you remember that…
we're in the same class in middle school?
But we weren't close back then.
Fuse.
What are you doing?
I'm solving the math homework that is due today.
But in high school,
we became close out of nowhere.
I'm so glad we got close.
You're always be by my side whenever I'm in trouble.
Even though I make you cry,
you never walk away.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry for making you sad.
But I won't let it happen again.
I'll care you the way you care me.
I'll understand you the way you understand me.
I'll take care of you the way you take care of me.
I will never hurt you.
Because I don't want to lose you again.
Tee.
Do you think…
we'll be together forever from now on?
Not as a friend.
But as a…
What?
Oh.
Oh!
Tee.
What's this?
Fuse.
A lot has happened recently.
It made me sad sometimes.
Fuse, I bought a cake for you.
And every good thing in your life,
you'd better keep it for yourself.
Can we go back to be friends?
Believe it or not,
I've never stopped loving you.
I'm so grateful for everything that…
brought me to a cutie like you.
You know what,
I like you from the first day.
When we got close,
I'm so happy.
You've meant more and more to me as time goes by.
You don't need to apologize at all.
I did it because I wanted to.
I'm not going anywhere…
because I love you.
From now on,
no matter what happens,
I'll never give up.
About what you asked…
if we'll stay together forever,
I think I can do it.
What about you? Can you do it?
I mean not as a friend.
Will you be my boyfriend?
I will, definitely.
Surprise!
You scared me.
I'm happy for you, Fuse.
Congrats.
Tee.
Take care of my friend.
I'll not only take care of him.
Huh?
I'll have him for keeps as well.
Ugh.
How long are you gonna keep farming aura?
You're farming aura too hard.
Wit.
Huh?
So, is the ghost story real?
Ah.
The ghost story.
Um.
It's not real. I made it up.
Oh.
Hey, is it scary?
If so, I'll share it on The Ghost Radio.
Alright, let's take a selfie to wrap up the day.
Com here.
Great.
I wonder, in the next ten years,
what you all will be doing?
Stop it.
We might fall.
We'd better go to school or we'll be late.
Just keep walking forward,
towards my future…
and my love.
Do you think I'm dreaming?
Dreaming?
I'm dreaming that we're a couple.
And it's our anniversary now.
Our anniversary?
Our one-hour anniversary.
Are you gonna count it in hours?
I'll count every minute.
Every hour.
Every day.
Every month.
And every year that we've been together.
Wow.
What if…
we broke up, would you still be friends with me?
You told me.
If we want good things to happen with us,
we must speak only good words.
So speak only good words, okay?
Can I kiss you?
We're a couple now. You can do whatever you want.
Close your eyes then.
[Darling]
Hello?
Are you up yet, darling?
When did you change your name in my phone?
You're already my boyfriend.
So I have to give you a proper nickname. Have you left yet?
I'm almost at school.
What? Why are you rushing to school?
I'm rushing to see my boyfriend.
You should hurry up and get here.
I'm waiting to go to class with you.
Alright, I'll be there soon.
Slow down, Fuse.
If you fall and hit your head,
I won't have time to take you to the hospital.
Um.
I'm just a little brother,
not like that person.
Ping.
What are we then?
Yeah.
You're just a little brother.
How could you ever compete with my girlfriend?
What did you say again?
Are we a couple?
Am I right?
Are we a couple now?
Now that you know, get going.
Fine.
Right, Jie.
I have something to tell you.
I also have my boyfriend.
I knew it for a while.
Huh?
You're still young, make sure you don't go too far.
You know what,
I already did it.
Fuse.
I'm kidding.
You can go now.
Alright, I'm leaving.
So, we're a couple now.
Right?
Hmm?
Um.
Really?
You always got it messy from your youth until your old age.
You always wipe it for me until we're old too.
Um, here.
Fuse.
Pa. Ma.
I have to go to school now.
Come here.
Hey, not completed yet.
Before leaving.
Ah.
So heartwarming. Look, someone is sulking.
Give your mom a kiss as well.
There, there.
Come on, just one quick kiss.
Alright.
See you later.
Take care, sweetheart.
Please have a seat.
Wait a sec.
Rice soup is here.
Did you make it yourself?
Nah, my mom made it.
Jeez, Frame.
But my mom's cooking is good,
so I brought some extra for you.
Okay.
Let's eat at my place next time.
Um.
Is it tasty?
It is, but not as tasty as you.
Such a sweet talker.
Hey.
Which number is this?
It's exactly the thousandth one.
Really?
Does this mean you get to make a wish now?
Yeah.
Not me, but you.
What? Why?
Well…
The person who can make a wish…
is the one to fold the thousandth one.
Huh? You mean me?
I stole it from you.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to steal it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You should make a wish.
Well,
I wish…
my boyfriend could make a wish.
See? Isn't it cool?
So you can make a wish now.
Um.
Well,
I wish my boyfriend a lot of happiness.
Hey, why that wish?
Because…
if you're happy,
I'm happy.
Whoa.
Such a sweet talker.
So…
What are you doing?
As long as you're here and fill my days,
I'm more than happy.
Hey.
Stop it.
We might fall.
What's wrong with you?
Hey.
You're so active. You go for a run in the morning…
and go for aerobics with me every afternoon.
Because I want to dance with you.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll run with you in the morning.
Seriously?
Um.
Waiting for you…
is lonely. I might as well run with you.
So we can stay together for a long time.
And you won't be looking at anyone else.
How could I look at someone else
when my boyfriend is this pretty?
Go take a shower and change your clothes.
Why? Am I smelly?
No, I just want to be the only one who gets to smell you like this.
Sniff me then.
You should go now.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Late and still playing around?
I'm not playing around, just saying hi to a friend.
Right, Locky?
We'd better go to school or we'll be late.
Give it to me.
Wait, tuck your shirt in.
At the back as well.
You are just like my dad.
Instead of calling you my happiness,
can I call you Daddy?
Hey.
You can't.
Why not?
I said no.
You can't call me like that.
I don't understand.
Alright, you can call me that in another three years.
Okay?
Okay, in another three years…
I'll call you my Daddy.
Fine, let's go.
Tee.
We'll be late.
Hurry up.
What?
It'll be like the last time.
Just a moment.
No, we should leave now.
Why are you surprised?
It's a ghost, not your teacher. Wait.
It's your teacher, not a ghost.
You're overreacting.
Thanyawat.
Teeratat. You guys are late again.
Get in the late line right now. Go.
See, we're late again.
You guys are always late for school.
Thanyawat, start a new line now.
Come here.
He can't.
We came together.
Does it have something to do with starting a new line?
What's the problem?
We're a couple.
Is that true, Thanyawat?
That's true.
Yes, they're together,
I saw it my own eyes.
Oh, so all of you already knew it?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Ugh.
That's great. As a couple,
you should guide each other in a good direction.
However, you arrive late at school,
you must get punished.
Do 30 squats.
Teacher, I have a boyfriend too.
You too?
Yes.
Who are you dating?
This guy.
Rodtang?
Book?
Are you really dating him?
Yes.
Teacher.
I have my happiness as well.
Where is your happiness?
This man.
Um, you two look good together.
Teacher.
Yes?
I also have a boyfriend.
Where is he?
He's at another school.
Oh my, why the students from this school so charming?
Teacher.
Do you have a boyfriend too?
I'm completely unwanted.
Ugh.
Alright.
So, you guys have to do 30 squats. All of you.
Get ready for it.
Come on, get yourself ready.
Teacher.
Hmm?
Yes, Teacher Lookmee.
Here is the document for you to sign.
Oh, okay.
Does it need to be signed today?
Yes, exactly.
Alright.
Yes.
Another page too.
Hey, these kids.
You're totally interrupting me.
They're students who are late for school.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm Rodtang.
I wonder, in the next ten years,
what you all will be doing?
In the next ten years? I think I would run a business.
I want to open a pet grooming salon.
Wow.
That's so sick.
And…
I probably take care of a kid.
A kid? Who?
Hey.
Just someone around here.
For me,
I'll take over the shop from my dad.
I'll expand my shop to ten branches.
Wow.
Rodtang and I will visit your shop.
That's cool, man.
I want to have children in the next ten years.
Hey.
Having children?
Isn't it a bit too soon?
I want to be a TikTok influencer.
Reviewing some products.
Do you think I could be an influencer?
Absolutely.
Of course.
For me,
I want to debut as a T-Pop artist.
Really?
Um.
Can I be your very first fan?
When my song goes viral…
and people use it for aerobics,
let's dance together.
Sure.
Whoa.
So sweet.
I might take a scholarship exam to study abroad.
Hey, what about me?
Can I go with you?
You can't.
You're dumb.
I'm going to study hard right now.
I hope you mean it.
For me,
I want to be a reporter.
Why?
Because I'm nosy.
Being nosy.
That's suit you.
Ten years from now on?
By then, I probably have graduated.
Started working and moved in with my boyfriend.
We'll see each other in the evenings
and go out together on weekends.
By that time, I'll probably keep walking.
Where to?
Just keep walking forward,
towards my future and my love.
I guess I'll just keep walking…
alongside this four-eyes next to me.
Gosh, that's so cute.
Can you stop recording? I'm gonna kiss my boyfriend.
Okay, sure.
See you again in ten years.
See you.
Bye bye.
Hey.
Go, let's go.